//these are the questions that will be referenced in the quiz with the correct answers and all of the choices 


let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is the name of this car part?",
    answer: "Alternator",
    options: [
      "",
      "",
      "",
      ""
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is the name of this car part?",
    answer: "Clutch Disc",
    options: [
      "",
      "",
      "",
      ""
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What is the name of this car part?",
    answer: "Connecting Rod",
    options: [
      "",
      "",
      "",
      ""
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What is the name of this car part?",
    answer: "Fuel Injector",
    options: [
      "",
      "",
      "",
      ""
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What is the name of this car part?",
    answer: "Head Gasket",
    options: [
      "",
      "",
      "",
      ""
    ]
},
{
    numb: 6,
    question: "What is the name of this car part?",
    answer: "Spark Plug",
    options: [
      "",
      "",
      "",
      ""
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What is the name of this car part?",
    answer: "Sway Bar",
    options: [
      "",
      "",
      "",
      ""
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What is the name of this car part?",
    answer: "Turbo Charger",
    options: [
      "",
      "",
      "",
      ""
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What is the name of this car part?",
    answer: "Valves",
    options: [
      "",
      "",
      "",
      ""
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What is the name of this car part?",
    answer: "Water Pump",
    options: [
      "",
      "",
      "",
      ""
    ]
},

]